You arrive with a real event, not a blank dashboard.
The first job is not a pitch. It is knowing what matters in this room.
Scroll through the event read, then tap a question or ask your own.
Research stays private. You decide what eventually gets shared.
Pick the two links that make sense for this event. Not every link belongs in every room.
The preview makes the privacy boundary obvious before anyone scans.
Share the pass instead of hunting for the right app, profile, or contact method.
The QR is designed for a real phone screen and a real conversation.
Capture the promise while it is fresh. Keep the context attached to the person.
The AI draft is editable. Copy it to the channel you already use, then mark it sent.
The goal is not more contacts. It is one real next step.